stream.me 2018-12-30

# Stream.me

We respect the privacy of the users of our website. We have developed this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our commitment to protecting the privacy of our users. We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully when using our website or our services. By using our website, you are accepting the terms and practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us.

## Information We May Collect

Generally, we may collect personal information about you, including information that can identify you (such as your name and email address) and other information that does not identify you. We may collect and store personal information about you that you provide to us or enter on our website, or that we otherwise obtain about you, such as personal information that may be contained in any content that you stream on our website or which you otherwise submit to our website.

We may also collect and store personal information about other people that you provide to us. If you use our website to stream or submit content, and such content contains personal information about others, such information may be collected and stored by us. If you use our website to send anything to others through our system, then we may collect and store the personal information of each such recipient. We may also periodically obtain both personal and non-personal information about you from affiliated and other third parties. Examples of information that we may receive include updated address information, purchase history, and additional demographic information.

When you visit our website, we may assign your computer one or more “cookies.” A “cookie” is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record keeping purposes. Cookies include session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie expires when you close your browser and is used to make it easier for you to navigate our website. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. Through the use of a cookie, we may collect information about your online activity on our website, such as the web pages you visit, the links you click, and the searches you conduct. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser settings to decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, please note that you may not be able to sign in or use some of the features of our website.

We automatically collect information from your browser when you visit our website. This information may include such things as your IP address, your browser type and language, access times, the content of any undeleted cookies that your browser previously accepted, and any referring website address.

We may use standard Internet technology, such as web beacons and other similar technologies, to track your use of our website. We also may include web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters to determine such things as whether messages have been opened and acted upon. The information we obtain in this manner enables us to customize the services we offer our website users to deliver targeted advertisements and to measure the overall effectiveness of our online advertising, content, programming or other activities.

## How We May Use the Information

We use email addresses to verify a user’s account and to communicate with users via notifications and site updates. We share these email addresses with Mandrill and MailGun, email providers who send these site notifications on our behalf. This data is stored until a user deletes their account.

We use IP addresses for fraud detection and to determine a user’s location. This data is stored until a user chooses to delete their account. We may continue to store an individual IP unlinked to a user, if that IP has been banned for violating our terms and conditions.

We use date of birth to verify that a user is at least 13 years of age, a requirement dictated in our terms and conditions. This data is stored until a user chooses to delete it.

We store PayPal email addresses, if submitted, to allow users to receive donations from other users on the site. We also store PayPal email addresses, if submitted, to pay out users money owed to them by the site such as subscriptions, sparkles and/or contest winnings. This data is stored until the user chooses to delete it.

We store physical addresses, if submitted, to mail checks or physical prizes. This data is stored until the user chooses to delete it.

We store payment tokens provided to us by payment providers, RocketGate, Xsolla, BrainTree and PayPal in order to enable recurring subscriptions, when opted into this feature. 

VODs (also known as archives) of streams, if enabled by the user, are kept on the site, publically available, for 45 days. They are then stored in a folder for deletion for 45 additional days, in case recovery is needed. Users can initiate deletion of publically available VODs at any time earlier than the 45 days or disable VODs at any time. User-deleted VODs are kept in a folder for deletion for the remainder of the original 45 days plus 45 additional days, in case recovery is necessary. Users can also extend the 45-day deadline via payment. 

Other than in certain unique situations discussed below, we do not share individualized personal information with third parties which we collect about our users, such as a user’s name or a user’s email address. We may share with third parties certain aggregated personal information about groups of users, such as average or range of ages of users, zip codes of users, etc. 

In certain unique situations, we reserve the right to share your individualized personal information when we believe disclosure is appropriate, such as in the following situations: *In response to a subpoena or similar investigative demand, a court order, a request for cooperation from a law enforcement or other government agency, or as otherwise required by law; *In connection with efforts to investigate, prevent, report or take other action regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud or other wrongdoing; *To protect, exercise, establish or defend the rights, property or safety of our users, our company, our employees, or others; *To enforce our website Terms and Conditions or other agreements or policies; or *In connection with a substantial corporate transaction or event, such as the sale of our business or assets, a merger, a consolidation, or a dissolution.

We may share aggregated or non-personal information we collect. We may share it with our affiliated companies, our business partner companies, or other third parties for different purposes, such as: (1) to tell our advertisers the number of visitors to our website and the most popular features or services; (2) to develop and deliver targeted advertising on our website or on websites of third parties; or (3) to conduct general business analysis. Also, this may be used to develop website content and services that we hope you and other users will find of interest.

## User Submitted Content

We provide areas on our websites where you can stream content, upload content, maintain your public profile, and message and live chat with other users. Any content you stream or submit is governed by our Terms and Conditions. Whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information on publicly-viewable web pages about yourself or others, that information will be publicly available and can be collected and used by us and others. We do not necessarily monitor, screen, or filter user submissions to our website, nor do we delete or scrape personal information from any such submissions. To the extent that any content or information that you stream or submit contains personal information (whether name, likeness, address, telephone number or otherwise, and whether such information pertains to the submitter or someone else), such personal information may be viewed by other users of our website. For example, if you submit your email address on a publicly-viewable area of our website, you may receive unsolicited messages. We cannot control who reads your submittals or what other users may do with the information you voluntarily submit on publicly-viewable areas, so we encourage you to exercise discretion and caution with respect to your submittals. Once you have submitted such information, you may not be able to edit or delete it.

## Third Party Websites

There may be a number of places on our website or through our services where you may access third party websites that do not operate under this Privacy Policy. For example, if you click on an advertisement on our website, you may be taken to a website that we do not control. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements or visit their websites. These third party websites may independently solicit and collect information, including personal information, from you and, in some instances, provide us with information about your activities on those websites. We recommend you consult the privacy policy of all third party websites you visit.

## How We Protect Your Personal Information

We take appropriate security measures (including electronic and procedural measures) to help safeguard your non-public personal information from unauthorized access and disclosure. For example, only authorized employees are permitted to access personal information, and they may do so only for permitted business functions. In addition, we use encryption in the transmission of your sensitive non-public personal information between your system and ours, and we use firewalls to help prevent unauthorized persons from gaining access to your non-public personal information.

We want you to feel confident using our website. However, no system can be completely secure. Therefore, although we take steps to secure your information, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information, searches, or other communications will always remain secure.

## Account Deletion and Request of Data

Users who wish to delete their account or request a copy of their data can do so by visiting their [Account Settings](https://www.stream.me/settings/account) page. Via the mobile app: tap on your user avatar in the upper right corner of the home screen, tap ‘edit’, tap ‘advanced options’.

Account deletion is permanent and data will be unrecoverable.

When a user requests a copy of their data, we will email a temporary link to access this data.

## No Rights of Third Parties

This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any personal information relating to users of our website.

## Changes to This Privacy Policy

We will occasionally update or modify this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices and services. When we make updates or modifications to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the "Last Updated" date at the bottom of this Privacy Policy. We recommend you review our Privacy Policy from time to time to inform yourself of any updates or modifications.

_Last Updated: May 25, 2018_
